

+380996638962 (Viber) dariaveretyak@gmail.com

Telegram: <u>@dariaveretyak</u> GitHub<u>: DariaVeretyak</u> <u>LinkedIn</u>

Kyiv, Ukraine, remote

Potrfolio

SKILLS

- Typescript, JavaScript (ES2015 2019)
- React, Redux, React Hook Form, React Router
- HTML5, CSS3, Sass (SCSS), BEM, Bootstrap, Material UI, Tailwind
- Fetch, REST API, Web sockets, Postman
- Figma
- Git/Github, VS Code, Chrome Developer Tools (incl. React), NPM
- Swiper, ChartJS, GSAP
- GULP, Webpack
- WordPress, OpenCart

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

- Frontend course at Mate academy
- FreeCodeCamp
- Learn.javascript.ru
- Developer.mozilla.org
- Reactjs.org
- CodeWars, LeetCode

Daria Veretyak

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Frontend Developer with solid knowledge of HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript (ES5, ES6), SASS, BEM, and version control systems GIT. I have experience with React and Redux Toolkit based on Typescript.

I have experience in developing sites for implementation on CMS (OpenCart, WP)

With more than 3 years experience an a Frontend Developer, I have acquired the skills necessary to build great and premium websites.

Experience

March 2024 - teel today

Frontend Developer, freelancer

December 2022 - March 2024

Promodex Agency, Frontend Developer

- developing user-friendly and responsive web-sites and support of existing projects;
- writing clean, modular, and maintainable code following coding standards;
- detection and elimination of errors;
- completion of all necessary tasks with high quality and within the set deadlines;
- code optimizing for performance and responsiveness on different devices;

Some of my projects you can see in my portfolio: Potrfolio

♦ June 2021-December 2022

Frontend Developer, freelancer

• 2012-2021

Logistics Manager in agriculture

9+ years of experience in logistics coordination for agricultural commodities and related agricultural products, 3 years as a Head of the logistics department

Education

National University of Life and Environmental Sciences of Ukraine, Kyiv

Master's Degree in Management of foreign economic activity 2006-2011